Jason Caldwell

Greater Denver Area, Colorado | jdcald13@gmail.com | http://www.jdcald13.com

Professional Summary

Objective: Seeking a Software Development or Quality Assurance Engineer Position. **Developer Training**: Skill Distillery coding bootcamp, MOOC, and self-study materials. **Software Experience**: Over 6.5 years of experience as a Quality Assurance Analyst and Software Support Specialist.

Education: Master of Business Administration (MBA) earning a GPA of 3.913. **Military**: Honorably discharged veteran who achieved the rank of Staff Sergeant. **Technologies**: Java, Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Git, GitHub, JUnit, Apache Tomcat, JIRA, and Rally.

Experience

Web Application Development with Java Skill Distillery Coding Bootcamp	September 2017 – Present Greater Denver Area
Programming Student Online and Self-Study Student	October 2016 – September 2017 Centennial, Colorado
Professional Poker Player Jason's Enterprises LLC	June 2015 – June 2017 Colorado and Nevada
Quality Assurance Analyst Tyler Technologies - Eagle Tax	February 2012 – May 2015 Lakewood, Colorado
Software Support Specialist Tyler Technologies - Eagle Assessor / Tax	October 2008 – February 2012 Lakewood, Colorado
324th Psychological Operations Company	April 2001 – April 2009

Education

United States Army Reserve

University of Colorado - Colorado Springs	Spring 2006 – Spring 2007
Master of Business Administration - MBA	Finance and Marketing: GPA 3.913
University of Colorado - Colorado Springs	Fall 2001 – Fall 2005
Bachelor of Science - BS	Business: GPA 3.854

Multiple locations around the world